



anggaawijaya90@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/anggaawijaya/



github.com/mittenpuss/



dribbble.com/mittenpuss/

#### PROFILE

Highly motivated IT magister student, with a strong background in computer science. Experienced in web development and agile development methodologies. Skilled in developing and implementing technical solutions to complex problems, focusing on user experience and performance.

#### SKILLS

Good understanding and skills in **Javascript**, **HTML and CSS** 

Good understanding and skills for creating a mockup and prototype using **Figma** 

Good understanding and skills for **Front End Web Development** using **React JS** 

Basic understanding and skills for **Back End Web Development** using **Node JS** and **Express JS** 

Experience in **Designing and Programming Database** using **MySQL** and **Oracle** 

Good understanding of **Agile Development Methodologies** 

Limited experience in using the **Google Cloud Platform** and **Amazon Web Services** to host
the database

## LANGUAGES

Indonesian

Native

English

Intermediate

TOEFL ITP: 587

# DEWA GEDE ANGGA WIJAYA

## FORMAL EDUCATION

#### UNIVERSITY OF INDONESIA (Aug 2021 - present) Temp. GPA: 3.5

Master Degree in Information Technology. Faculty of Computer Science

**Activities**: Became a teaching assistant for **Computer Information Systems** courses and coordinated with lecturers to assist 36 students with their assignments and provide feedback

**Thesis**: Evaluation and Interface Design Improvement Recommendations for Toyota Trust E-Commerce Website: A Study Case of PT Astra Auto Trust

## UDAYANA UNIVERSITY (graduated in 2020) GPA: 3.27

Bachelor in Computer Science. Faculty of Mathematics and Natural Sciences.

Activities: Active as a member of Student Council on Faculty of Mathematics and Natural Sciences

Final Project: Android-based Balinese Language Learning Application Using Knuth-Morris-Pratt Algorithm

## NON FORMAL EDUCATION —

#### DIGITAL TALENT SCHOLARSHIP, FRESH GRADUATE ACADEMY

Database Design and Programming with SQL (Sept - Nov 2020)

The Ministry of Communication and Information Technology selected me for the scholarship. I learned how to design and program a well-structured database. The program is completely done online because of the pandemic. Learning resources were taught using **Oracle Academy** and creating the Database using **Oracle Data Modeler.** We used **Oracle Application Express (APEX)** for the Software Development Environment.

#### **SANBERCODE ONLINE BOOTCAMP** (July-Oct 2020)

React JS Development and Intermediate React Native Mobile Development

Learned various skill in React JS and React Native Mobile Development.

Fundamental: Gitlab

Front End: React Hooks

Mobile: Finger Print Authentification, Mapbox, Realtime Data Management, and Deep Linking

#### PURWADHIKA CODING AND STARTUP SCHOOL (Jan - July 2020)

**Web and Mobile Development Programme** 

Became the best graduate from the current batch, which consist of 21 people. I also learned various skills in Web and Mobile Development.

Fundamental: Data Structure, Algorithm, Javascript, HTML, CSS, Git, Github.

Front End: React JS, Redux.

Back-End: NodeJS, ExpressJS, MySQL, MongoDB, RESTful API, Postman.

Mobile: React Native, React Navigation.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE** -

## PERUM PERURI (Sept 2023 - present)

HR Management System Planning and Development Section (Contract)

Passed the RBB BUMN.

- Develop and manage HR management systems and policies in general.
- Develop and manage changes to the organizational structure and derivative products.
- Carrying out job evaluations in accordance with the company organization.

#### RESEARCH ASSISTANT (Early 2018 - Dec 2018)

- Assisting lecturer with their research and occasionally helping researchers from abroad that are coming to Bali and needs help researching Balinese Culture.
- In charge of research conferences held by the Faculty of Cultural Sciences at Udayana University.
   I made all event designs, from pamphlets and certificates to book covers.

#### **INTERNATIONAL GLOBAL NETWORK** (Apr - Dec 2018)

#### Campus Ambassador

- Dealing with enquiries from local press, NGOs, and related organizations, establishing and maintaining the relationship.
- Actively promote IGN events in the local environment and become a committee for MUN events in countries such as Malaysia, and Indonesia.

#### **UDAYANA UNIVERSITY, VETERINARY DEPT.** (May - Oct 2017)

## IT Staff Internship

- Cooperated with other interns to create a veterinary master's student registration system using PHP and HTML that integrated with the faculty's website.
- Responsible as a liaison between administrative staff and students, performing various data entries for student needs into the system.

## RECENT EXPERIENCES IN ORGANIZATION AND EVENT

- Bali Asia International Model United Nations 2019. BAIMUN (Volunteer)
- Youth Excursion 2017 in Seoul, South Korea. YOUTEX (Selected Participant)
- 2nd Global Young Leaders Peace Camp in Sri Lanka 2017. GYLPC (Selected Participant)
- 32nd ICSU General Assembly in Bali 2017 (Liaison Officer)